Inventory of the Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
- Posters, 1950-
  - 1990s- (Folder 4)
    - Photograph of Jeffrey Scott Wifaner? '94. Football.
    - Steve Reich. Distinguished American Composer. John Spencer Camp Lecture. World Music Hall, CFA. December 9 1997.
    - Peoples Awareness Month 1992. Wesleyan Asian/Asian American Student Union. Funded by Wes Student Assembly.
    - Wesleyan Student Films. CFA Cinema, May 8-10, 1992.
    - Stone Reader: A Documentary Film for People Who Love Books. November 11, 2004. Premier Event of The Friends of the Wesleyan Library. Signed by Participants: Dow Mossman and Mark Moskowitz.
- Posters, Early to 1949
  - 1909-1937 (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
    - Krying Kids Take Kare, by Oscar F. Cargill, class of 1922, printed in the fall of 1919, with drawing and poem about the rivalry between freshmen and sophomores
      Given by Sally L. Adams, granddaughter of Oscar F. Cargill, April 2010
    - The Wesleyan Dramatic Association Presents: The Good Natured Man. By Oliver Goldsmith. Poli's Theatre, Meriden. Feb 22 1909.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Presents Aren't We All? A comedy in Three acts by Frederick Lonsdale. '92 Theatre. March 3, 1931.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Present Last Year's Nest. A modern comedy y John Swain. '92 Theater-Rich Hall. Dec 18 1933.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University and Professor Erwat Matthews Present Criminal at Large. A mystery play by Edgar Wallace. '92 Theatre - Rich Hall. Nov 27, 1934.
    - Second Performance. The Class of 1938 Presents The Critic. '92 Theatre - Rich Hall. March 20 1935.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Presents Julius Caesar. '92 Theatre -- Rich Hall. April 26 and 29, 1935. Poster w/ attached photos.
    - Twelfth Night. With John Lincoln as Sebastian and Eleanor Flagg as Viola. '92 Theater - Rich Hall. April 21 and 22, 1936. Poster w/ attached photos.
    - Twelfth Night. With Walter Bennett as Valentine and Brown, Thomas, and Figgens as Courtiers. '92 Theater - Rich Hall. April 21 and 22, 1936.
    - Waiting for Lefty. By Clifford Odets. '92 Theatre - Rich Hall. Oct 29 and 30, 1936.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Presents a Production for Christmas, The Pageant of the Shearman and the Tailors. '92 Theatre - Rich Hall. December 10 1936.
    - The Wig and Candle Club of Connecticut College and The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Presents present The Dover Road by A. A. Milne. '92 Theatre - Rich hall. Feb 23, 1937.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Presents The Emperor Jones. Starring Mr. Franklin Webb. '92 Theatre - Rich Hall. Oct 14-15, 1937.
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University Present a revival of The Pageant of the Shearmen and the Tailors. A miracle Play for Christmas. '92 Theatre - Rich Hall. Dec 16, 1937.
  - 1938-1949 (Folder 2)
    - Wings Over Europe. The '92 Theater. Nov. 13-15, 1946
    - Berkeley Square. The '92 Theater. Apr. 10-12, 1946
    - You Can't Take It With You. The '92 Theater. May 22-24, 1946
    - Macbeth. The '92 Theater. Apr. 14-19, 1947
    - The Inspector General. The '92 Theater. Jan. 30-Feb. 1, 1946
    - Three One Act Plays. The '92 Theater. Dec. 4-6, 1947
    - You Can't Take It With You. The '92 Theater. May 22-24, n.d.
    - Cox and Box: A Comic Opera in One Act. A production of the Paint and Powder Club and the Glee Club of Wesleyan University. The '92 Theater. Mar. 5, 1938
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University has the honor of presenting the premiere production of Yankee Doodle: A Drama of the American Revolution. '92 Theater. Apr. 8-9, 1938
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University presents Transient Breath: A Fantastic Comedy. '92 Theater. Nov. 19 and Nov. 21, 1938
    - Tovarich, A Paint and Powder Club Production. '92 Theater. Feb. 4 and 6, 1939
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan Presents Its Annual Spring Production: Little Lord Fauntleroy: A Burleque With An All Male Cast. '92 Theater. Apr 21 and 24, 1939
    - Did It Ever Occur To You To Strike Her In The Face? The Paint and Power Club of Wesleyan University Presents Ways and Means and Hands Across The Sea. '92 Theater. Oct. 31 and Nov. 8, 1941
    - Our Town. '92 Theater. Nov. 27-29, 1945
    - Three One Act Plays. The '92 Theater. Dec. 4-6, 1947
    - Antigone. The '92 Theater. Feb. 19-21, 1948
    - She Stoops To Conquer. '92 Theater. Apr. 12-17, 1948
    - Candida. '92 Theater. Nov. 15-20, 1948
    - Doctor Faustus. '92 Theater. Apr. 25-29, 1949
  - 1884-1938 (Folder 3)
    - Wesleyan University Glee Club Concert and Dance. Dec. 30, [1926-27]
    - Wesleyan Musical Association: The Girl and the Graduate. Academy of Music. April 24, n.d.
    - Wesleyan Glee and Mandolin Clubs. Mary Lyon Chapel. Jan. 16, 1906.
    - Who's Got Winifred? Better Find Out! Wesleyan Prom Show. Middlesex Theater. May 8, 1914
    - Concert by the Wesleyan College Glee Club. The Tabernacle. Jul. 19, 1888
    - The Paint and Powder Club of Wesleyan University presents College Bred or The Four Year Loaf: A Musical Revue in 14 Scenes. Apr. 29 and May 3, 1938
    - Grand Concert by the Wesleyan College Glee Club. Newichawanic Hall South, Berwick. Jan. 1, 1884
    - Concert, The Wesleyan Glee Club. Town Hall, Windsor. Jan. 13, 1886.
    - Grand Concert Given By Wesleyan University Glee Club. Wyoming Seminary Chapel, Kingston PA. April 8, 1887.
    - Concert Given By the Wesleyan University Glee Club. Town Hall, Wellesley, MA. May 7, 1887.
    - Grand Concert Given By the Wesleyan University Glee Club. Congregational Church, Terryville, CT. Jan 24, 1888.
    - Grand Concert! By the Wesleyan Glee Club Assisted by Miss Olive Browe the Charming Reader From Boston. At the Opera House [New Britain CT]. Mar. 19, 1888.
    - Coming: The Glee Club of Wesleyan University. Association Hall. Apr. 11, 1888
    - Wesleyan Glee Club Will Give a Concert. Windsor Town Hall, May 23, 1888.
    - Concert By College Glee Club. Redbank Opera House. Jul. 18, 1888.
  - Nineteenth Century (Folder 4)
    - Wesleyan University Marshall's Notice '98. Jun. 29, 1898.
    - College Chapel Annual Mid-Winter Concert by the Wesleyan Glee and Mandolin Clubs Assisted by Mr William B. Davis!. Feb. 7, ca. 1890s
  - Untitled (Folder 5)
    - Cito Maturum, cito putridum. Joke poster for Washington's birthday, Feb. 21, 1861.
    - Wesleyan University Celebration of Washington's Birthday: Oration by Wilbur A. Mott, Declamation by Harry H. Kynett. Feb. 22, 1882.
    - Washington's Birthday Celebration! Oration by G. Downey, Declamation by D. Beattys, Music by the Glee Club. Feb. 22, 1884.
  - (Folder 6)
    - The Campus Chest Budget. Wesleyan Christian Association. Paint and Magic Marker on Poster board, ca. 1937
    - All Veterans Register Here, ca. 1946, painted sign on cardboard.
  - (Folder 7)
    - Marshal's Notice, 1898. Members of the Board of Trustees, the Faculty, the Alumni and Invited Guests, together with the graduating class and candidates for a master's degree. Jun. 29, 1898. At the Chapel of the Methodist Church. 20" x 12 1/2"
    - Annual Mid-winter Concert by the Wesleyan Glee and Mandolin Clubs. Assisted by Mr. William B. Davis. Feb 7, 1895.
- Miscellany
  - Maps From Olin Government Documents (Drawer 6)
    - U.S. Coast Survey: Lines of Equal Magnetic Declination For the Year 1850. 1856. Map of United States.
    - Sketch "A" Showing Progress in No. 1, U.S. Coast Survey 1844-1850. Map of New England Coast.
    - A Map of the Isle of Cuba with the Bahama Islands, Gulf of Florida and Windward Passage: Drawn from English and Spanish Surveys. Engraved by Thomas Jefferys, Geographer to His Majesty. 1768.
    - Profiles of the Actual Curves of Daily Oscillations at the Several Stations on the Five Great Lakes and Detroit River, Showing the Effects of Wind and Storms on Each Place for the Month of October 1859.
    - Profiles of the Mean Monthly and Five Day Curves of the Water Levels at the Several Stations of Observations on the Five Great Lakes and Detroit River for the Year Commencing September 1859 and Ending August 1860.
    - Profile of the Curves of the Annual Oscillations in the Five Great Lakes and Detroit River for Ten Years, from 1851 to 1861.
    - Sketch Showing the Progress of the Survey and the arrangement of General and Preliminary Charts published and in progress of publication. 1860. Map of Great Lakes.
    - Survey of the N.& N.W. Lakes. Showing the Progress of the Survey in Lake Michigan. 1861.
    - Geological Map of the United States. Compiled by C.H. Hitchcock and W.P. Blake. 1872.
    - Sunoco Auto Road Map of Connecticut, Rhode Island, Massachusetts. 1935.
    - Map of Midwestern United States. 1856.
    - Map of the Territory of the United States from the Mississippi to the Pacific Ocean. Ordered by the Hon. Jeff'n Davis, Secretary of War to Accompany the Reports of the Explorations for a Railroad Route. 1854. Written on map is 1857
    - Road Map of the Northeastern United States: World's Fair Edition. 1940.
  - Godard Library
    - The Gift of the Godard Library to Wesleyan University, 1937.
    - The Gift of the Godard Library to Wesleyan University, undated
  - Foss House
    - Matted watercolor, signed E.L. Jacobs, Jan. 1955
  - Douglas Cannon
    - Matted color photograph of the Cannon with text, Dear Wesleyan, From the oldest alumnus still around, happy birthday Wesleyan! -Douglas W. Cannon. 1981.
  - Mystical Seven Templum Project Models, circa 1999
    - M-7 Templum Project. Sheet describing the aesthetic of the architecture. 5 copies. No Date.
    - Translucent Drawing of figure near temple. No Date.
    - Translucent Drawing of stairwell. No Date.
    - Map of Wesleyan University without legend or text. No date.
    - Map of the roads of Wesleyan University without legend or text. No date.
    - Map of the fields of Wesleyan University without legend or text. No date.
    - Map of the buildings of Wesleyan University without legend or text. No date.
    - Map of a river. No text or legend. No date.
    - Map of a city. No text or legend. No date.
    - Sheet of paper with various green blotches. No date.
    - Sheet of paper with squares and designs. No date.
    - Sheet of paper with squares and designs. No date.
    - Sheet of paper with lines and numbers. Seven heavens, seven stars, seven planets, seven days of the week, seven wise men of Greece, seven kings of the seven hilled city. Possibly a calendar marked 2000 and 2003. 2 copies.
    - Sheet of paper with numbers and lines. 1837-1912. 2 copies.
    - Sheet of paper with squares and designs. No date.
    - Sheet of paper with squares and designs and legend of designs. No date.
    - Sheet of paper with 8 photographs of glass jars
    - Sheet of paper with 8 photographs of glass jars
    - Sheet of paper with 8 photographs of glass jars
    - Matted Translucent Drawing of figure near temple.
    - Matted Translucent Drawing of Stairwell
    - Matted Translucent Drawing of Stairwell.
    - Revealing Views of Architectural Elements mat board with various diagrams of M-7 temple.
    - Mystical (of course) Mat board with seven photographs of M-7 temple model.
    - M-7 Templum Project. Maps of Wesleyan University and Middletown on a mat board.
    - Laminated Glass and Point fixing with out a drilled hole photographs of glassware and diagrams on mat board.
  - Baseball
    - Muffins! Grand Trial of Skill!! The Senior and Junior Classes of Wesleyan University will give an Exabition of the curious and interesting Game of Muffins on Saturday, April 28. 1866. Baseball poster.
  - Sigma Xi
    - Parchment proclaiming the Charter for the establishment of a Chapter of the Society of the Sigma Xi at Wesleyan University, Apr. 25, 1935
  - Early Newspaper Accounts of the University
    - Listing of students and faculty, 1887-1888.
    - Listing of students and faculty, 1890-1891.
    - Listing of students and faculty, 1891-1892.
    - Card describing a mention of Wesleyan University in the Middlesex Gazette. Olin Library.
    - Card describing a mention of Wesleyan University and President Fisk in The Sentinel and Witness. Olin Library.
    - The Middlesex Gazette, Jul. 15, 1829.
    - Description of various articles in newspapers mentioning Wesleyan from 1829-1831.
    - The New-York Spectator, Nov. 19, 1830.
    - Christian Advocate and Journal and Zion's Herald, Jul. 22, 1831.
    - Badger's Weekly Messenger, Sep. 28, 1831.
    - Wesleyan University, Middletown, Conn. With engraving of campus, in Christian Advocate and Journal and Zion's Herald, Dec. 28, 1832.
  - Other Items
    - The Wesleyan University Certificate of Scholarship, 3 copies, undated
    - Wesleyan Coat of Arms, matted watercolor, 1953
    - Poem. Contexts by Paul Monette. Apr. 14, 1977.
    - Monotony, the Game of Olin Librarian Ship. Joke board game with photographs of Olin Librarians and rules. December, 1977.
  - Wesleyan Banner
    - Felt, 31" x 14," ca. 1943 [Accession number 2003-20]
- Individuals
  - 5 men, 1 woman, unidentified photo, ca. 1890. One man is George W. Davison '92. (Drawer 7)
  - President Shanklin Inaugural Newspapers
    Note: Fragile. See Vertical File for photocopies
    - Middletown Sun, Nov. 12, 1909. Rousing Welcome by The People to Taft and Sherman Who Come Here in Honor of Wesleyan and Shanklin.
    - The Hartford Courant, Nov. 13, 1909. Middletown Citizens Give a Royal Welcome to President Taft.
    - The Hartford Courant, Nov. 8, 1909. Wesleyan's Great Week.
    - The Penny Press. Nov. 12, 1909. Wesleyan Honored by President Taft at Installation of President Shanklin.
    - The Middletown Sun. Nov. 13, 1909. Best Time Here, Says Pres. Taft.
  - Sam Green Festschrift: A Tribute to Sam Green Since 1948 [1974]. Organized by J. W. Reed, Jr. 22 1/2" x 17 1/2"
  - Andrus family genealogical chart
  - Fred B. Millet, pencil and chalk portrait by Carolyn Edmundson, Mar. 25, 1928. 20 x 12 1/2
  - Individual Images
    - Photograph of oil painting of Joseph Beech, class of 1899.
    - Photo of Reuben Bennet, class of 1897.
    - Photo of unknown man.
    - Engraving of unknown man.
    - Newspaper clipping, Wilbert Snow, Governor 13 Days.
    - Photograph of Hubert Goodrich, plus negatives.
  - Photographic Portrait of Burton H. Camp, '01, and His Sister as Children (ca. 1890)
  - Caleb T. Winchester Portrait Photo
  - Myron C. Cramer '04, portrait
  - Max Tishler Laboratory of Organic Chemistry: copy printout of dedication banner, October 30, 2001
- Groups (Photographs)
  - Prof. E.E. Schattschneider and Class - Trip to Washington Photo, 1938 (Drawer 8)
  - Building Crew, North college, 1893. Photo of workers on the front steps of North College, with a letter from the State Librarian describing the picture.
  - Carbon Club - New York, 1935, photo.
  - Caleb T. Winchester, William North Rice, possibly Slocum in Rear. Taken by K. Van Dyke. Ca. 1916.
  - A.C. Armstrong, (in background), William North Rice, and Caleb T. Winchester. Ca. 1919.
  - About 1919. C.T. Winchester [right] and W.N. Rice [left] emerging from Memorial Chapel; Behind them, Prof. A.C. Armstrong. Professor Winchester died in 1920.
  - Faculty of Wesleyan, 1957. Identification in Olla Podrida, 1958.
  - Library staff collage, matted on foamcore board, ca. early 1990s
  - Wesleyan Dramatic Club Photos, 1911-1912
    - Wesleyan University Dramatic Club. Photo by Brucker.
    - Dramatic Club 1912. Attributions listed.
    - The Dramatic Club, 1912; 'You Never Can Tell,' by G. Bernard Shaw. Attributions listed.
    - Dramatic Club 1911. Attributions listed.
    - The Title Mart - 1911. Gibbs, '13 (Tilton), Crane '13 (Tredbury), Leonard '12 (Berking), Robertson '12 (Ezra), Morningstar, '11 (Edith). Plaza Hotel, N.Y. Photo by Drocker and Co, NY.
    - The Title Mart - 1911. Attributions listed.
  - Class of 1893, 25th reunion, June 15, 1918.
  - Class of 1893, taken June 17, 1922.
  - Senior Year, ATT- Front row -3rd from right (Arthur T. Talmadge)
  - Twenty-Fifth Reunion, Class of 1919, University Club, New York City, June 2, 1944. Attributions listed.
  - Class of 1869.
  - Welcome Wet Wunn: Lines to A Freshman, on his First Birthday. Gift of Ev Graham '24.
  - 2 copies, Wesleyan University, R.O.T.C. 1918. Panoramic photo of soldiers on Andrus field
  - Panoramic photo, class of 1936?
  - Untitled panoramic photograph of the entire student body in front of College Row, undated
  - Student body, 1931, panoramic photo
  - Student body, 1931. Titled Wesleyan University College Body - 1931 - September. Al Bell '35. Gift of John Horland '35 7/90.
  - Student body, 1923, large panoramic photo
- Teams, Clubs and Fraternities
  - Wesleyan Glee Club at the U.S. Capital March, 1935, with accompanying key. (Drawer 9)
  - Class of 1873 Boat Club Records and Rowing Scrapbooks, Collection 1000-10, Oversize Series
    - Eight Regatta of the Harlem Regatta Association, Jun. 9, 1882.
    - Map of Saratoga Lake with Rowing Courses for College Regatta, 1875.
    - The Great College Regatta at Springfield Mass, July 17th, Frank Leslies' Illustrated Newspaper, Aug. 2, 1873.
  - Fraternities
    - Psi Upsilon, ca. 1921-25. Property of John C.R. Whiteley, Xi of Psi Upsilon.
    - Sigma Lambda Nu 1919 - Upsilon - 1920
    - John Cecil Rushworth Whiteley's diploma for Bachelor of Philosophy. June 8, 1925.
    - John Wesley Club, 1955
    - Delta Sigma, 1961
    - Delta Sigma, 1962
    - Kappa Alpha Society, 1970
    - Kappa Alpha Society, 1970
    - Diploma for Donald Balch Summers, Kappa chapter of Sigma Xi, Mar. 10, 1932.
    - Gamma Zeta, 1905
    - Kappa Nu Kappa, 1967
  - Sports Teams
    - Dedication. Poster of crew team on the water. Attached to verso is an article about the dedication of the Macomber Boathouse, Oct. 16, 1993.
    - Dedication. Poster of runners, one wearing a Wesleyan jersey, undated
    - Victory Dinner of the Wesleyan Football Team, Dec. 15, 1947
    - Football team photo [?], 1915
    - Wesleyan-41 Williams-6, football photo, Nov. 6, 1915.
    - 1913 Baseball Squad. Collection of J.R. Holmes '14.
    - 1912-13 Football Team photo (10½ x 13½, mounted on cardboard)
  - Kappa Gamma photo: Wesleyan Kai Gar Class of 1898. Taken in Spring of 1895.
  - Kappa Gamma photo: June 12, 1948 - 50th Reunion Class of 1898 - Wesleyan University.
  - Debate Club: Eastern Intercollegiate Debate Champions 1930-31
  - Debate Club: Eastern Intercollegiate Debate Champions 1926-27
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs
    - 5th Annual New England Intercollegiate Glee Club Contest. Auditorium, Springfield, Mass. Feb. 28, 1930.
    - Wesleyan Glee and Mandolin Clubs, circa 1879.
    - Wesleyan University Glee Club at U.S. Capitol, March 1935. New England Champions-1935.
    - Glee and Mandolin Clubs, circa 1879
    - Wesleyan Glee and Mandolin Clubs, circa 1879.
    - Glee and Mandolin Clubs. 1912-13.
  - Wesleyan Dramatic Club
    - The Dramatic Club, 1909.
    - Wesleyan University Dramatic Club in 'The Good Natured Man' By Oliver Goldsmith. 1909.
    - The Good Natured Man, cast photo, 1909.
    - Captain Letterblair, cast photo, 1910.
  - Penn-Wesleyan Championship Football Match, Color poster advertisement, Nov. 24, 1892
- Buildings - Photos
  - Aerial views (Drawer 10)
    - Aerial view of campus, circa 1931-1933.
    - Aerial view of campus during the Foss Hill dorm construction. Negative number 32/09. Unframed 2/76.
    - Aerial view of campus, ca. 1950. (2)
    - Aerial view of campus, 1946.
    - Aerial view of campus, undated
    - Aerial view of campus, Alumni Day, Jun. 22, 1946.
  - Engraving of Russell House, ca. 1831.
  - Photograph of Russell House. From N. Campbell, 6/88.
  - Large obituary of Karl Pomeroy Harrington, 1861-1953, 4 copies
  - College Row
    - College Row, 1909. With note from Michael J. Durkan on back, 1970.
    - College Row, 1909. Duplicate copy.
    - Print of old North College, before March, 1906. Gift of Burton H. Camp '01, Jan. 19, 1972.
    - College Row, n.d.
    - College Row, n.d., unframed 2/76.
    - Print of '92 theatre and Chapel, n.d.
  - Photograph of the group of workmen who renovated and modernized North College (Article in the Alumnus entitled North College Once Scene of Stirring Race Against Time.)
  - Campus Maps
    - Hand drawn Map of Wesleyan, 1937
    - Printed Map, 1930
    - Color Printed Map, 1931
  - Memorial Chapel, wallpaper sample, ca. 1870s
  - Freeman Athletic Center Grand Opening, Mar. 31, 1990, 3 copies
  - Map of Middletown, including businesses, ca. late 1990s. Produced and distributed by Jin Som '94.
- Buildings - Renderings
  - Proposed Library Architecture: 7 photo prints, Perry, Dean, Rogers, 1982 (Drawer 11)
  - HiRise, architect's color rendering, n.d.
  - Sketch of proposed library building next to Olin, on site of Davenport campus center (2)
  - Wesleyan Buildings - Watercolors and Prints
    - Drawing of the University, Richard Rummel, n.d.
    - Inauguration of William Chace, September 23, 1989, 4 drawings
    - Drawing of North and South College used in brochure of poems published by DKE, spring 1946.
    - Drawing of North and South Colleges and the chapel, Allen Tompkins, n.d. Unframed, 2/76.
    - Painting of North and South Colleges and the chapel. "Brownstone Row, 1900, Vignette of old Eclectic House," n.d.
    - Drawing of North and South College, matted, n.d.
  - Olin Renderings
    - Color Sketch of Olin Library.
    - Black and White sketch of Olin Library.
  - McKim, Mead, & White Renderings
    - Drawing of Harriman Hall.
    - Drawing of North College and the Squash Courts.
    - Drawing of Olin and Harriman.
  - John Wesley House/Downey House
    - Drawing of Downey House
    - Drawing of Downey House with map.
  - Foss Hill Dormitories
    - Drawing of Foss Hill Dormitories, Lounge A, South Elevation.
    - Watercolor of Foss Hill Dorms.
    - Watercolor of Lounge A, by Marshall Field and Company.
    - Drawing of Foss Hill Dorms
    - Drawing of Connecting Corridor Between Units 6 and 5 of Lounge C. West Elevation.
    - Drawing of an interior view of a typical dorm room, with diagrams.
  - PAC and North-South College Connector
    - Drawing of the connection between North and South College
    - Watercolor of Public Affairs Center.
  - Unidentified
    - Sketch of unidentified building.
    - Sketch of Malcolm X House.
    - Sketch of proposed walkway between chapel and '92 Theatre.
  - Infirmary: map of grounds.
  - Sketch of proposed inn at Middletown
  - Sketch of McConaughy Hall.
- Buildings: Olin Library and McKim, Mead & White Campus
  - Olin Library Images (Drawer 12)
    - Olin entrance and circulation desk taken from above, photo, undated
    - Olin front columns at night, photo, undated
    - Color Photograph of Olin, surrounded by trees in bloom, undated
    - Olin, circa 1986
    - 4 large negatives of Olin.
    - Entrance and chandelier, photo, undated
    - Reading room, basement level, photo, ca. 1967.
    - Periodicals room, photo, ca. 1967.
    - Periodicals room with student, photo, ca. 1967.
  - McKim, Mead & White Campus Plans, 1925-26, 1932
    - Cross Street, blueprint.
    - Park Street, blueprint.
    - Campus blueprint
    - Campus blueprint II
    - Campus blueprint III
    - Campus blueprint with locations drawn in red.
  - General Plan, February 1956.
  - Carbon Copy of campus map. Tan paper with purple ink.
  - Olin Library, 1980
    - A Study of Stained Glass Windows for the Dietrich Room in the Olin Library, watercolor, undated
    - Sketch of the expansion of Olin Library, by Perry, Dean, Rogers & Partners.
    - Sketch of the inside of the expanded Olin in faint red ink.
    - Sketch of the East elevation of the proposed Dietrich reading room. Duplicate